<xml>
<quote>    Real, constructive mental power lies in the creative thought that shapes your destiny, and your hour-by-hour mental conduct produces power for change in your life. Develop a train of thought on which to ride. The nobility of your life as well as your happiness depends upon the direction in which that train of thought is going.
                        [#808080]Laurence J. Peter (1919 - 1988)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    if Jerry Brown is the answer, it must be a very peculiar question.
                        [#808080]Sen Lloyd Bentsen, D-Texas[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I've never been married, but I tell people I'm divorced so they won't think something's wrong with me.
                        [#808080]Elayne Boosler[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Americans are overreachers; overreaching is the most admirable of the many American excesses.
                        [#808080]George F. Will (1941 - ), Statecraft as Soulcraft[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There is nothing in the world so much admired as a man who knows how to bear unhappiness with courage.
                        [#808080]Seneca (5 BC - 65 AD)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Opportunity knocked. My doorman threw him out.
                        [#808080]Adrienne Gusoff[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There is an art of which every man should be a master the art of reflection. If you are not a thinking man, to what purpose are you a man at all?
                        [#808080]William Hart Coleridge[/#]</quote>

<quote>    ...Clean up complexion, soften eye lines, soften smile line, add color to lips, trim chin, remove neck lines, soften line under ear lobe, add highlights to earrings, add blush to cheek, clean up neck line, remove stray hair, remove hair strands from dress, adjust color and add hair on top of head, add dress on side to create better line... Total: $1,525.00.
                        [#808080]The invoice for retouching the cover photo of Michelle Pfeiffer, in the December 1990, issue of Esquire magazine, obtained by Harper's. The photo's caption reads, "What Michelle Pfeiffer Needs...Is Absolutely Nothing."[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The greatest pleasure in life is doing what people say you cannot do.
                        [#808080]Walter Bagehot (1826 - 1877)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If you talk enough, you don't feel you have to _do_ anything.
                        [#808080]John Updike's mother[/#]</quote>

<quote>    One of the simple but genuine pleasures in life is getting up in the morning and hurrying to a mousetrap you set the night before.
                        [#808080]Kin Hubbard (1868 - 1930)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    People are very fond of giving away what they need most themselves. It is what I call the depth of generosity.
                        [#808080]Oscar Wilde (1854 - 1900), The Picture of Dorian Grey[/#]</quote>

<quote>    No matter what we have come through, or how many perils we have safely passed, or how many imperfect and jagged - in some places perhaps irreparably - our life has been, we cannot in our heart of hearts imagine how it could have been different. As we look back on it, it slips in behind us in orderly array, and, with all its mistakes, acquires a sort of eternal fitness, and even, at times, of poetic glamour.
                        [#808080]Randolph Silliman Bourne[/#]</quote>

<quote>    In all human affairs there are efforts, and there are results, and the strength of effort is the measure of the results.
                        [#808080]James Allen[/#]</quote>

<quote>    In the begining there was nothing, and it exploded.
                        [#808080]Terry Pratchett, (on the big bang theory)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I caused my husband's heart attack. In the middle of lovemaking I took the paper bag off my head. He dropped the Polaroid and keeled over and so did the hooker. It would have taken me half an hour to untie myself and call the paramedics, but fortunately the Great Dane could dial.
                        [#808080]Joan Rivers (1935 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If you haven't found something strange during the day, it hasn't been much of a day.
                        [#808080]John A. Wheeler[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Everyone woman has a flaw. If it is not on the exterior it's in her head.
                        [#808080]Dan Marquardt[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There is danger in both belief and unbelief.
                        [#808080]Phaedrus (15 BC - 50 AD)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The idea of perfect closes your mind to new standards.. When you drive hard toward one ideal, you miss opportunities and paths, not to mention hurting your confidence. Believe in your potential and then go out and explore it; don’t limit it.
                        [#808080]John Eliot, Ph.D., Reverse Psychology for Success[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Journalists cover words and delude themselves into thinking they have committed journalism.
                        [#808080]Hedrick Smith[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Ignorance of the law excuses no man: Not that all men know the law, but because 'tis an excuse every man will plead, and no man can tell how to refute him.
                        [#808080]John Selden (1584 - 1654)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Too many of us wait to do the perfect thing, with the result we do nothing. The way to get ahead is to start now. While many of us are waiting until conditions are "just right" before we go ahead, others are stumbling along, fortunately ignorant of the dangers that beset them. By the time we are, in our superior wisdom, decided to make a start, we discover that those who have gone fearlessly on before, have, in their blundering way, traveled a considerable distance. If you start now, you will know a lot next year that you don't know now, and that you will not know next year, if you wait.
                        [#808080]The William Feather Magazine[/#]</quote>

<quote>    What is defeat? Nothing but education; nothing but the first step to something better.
                        [#808080]Wendell Phillips (1811 - 1884)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I was brought up to believe that the only thing worth doing was to add to the sum of accurate information in the world.
                        [#808080]Margaret Mead (1901 - 1978)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Wasting sarcasm is a sin.
                        [#808080]R. Stevens, Diesel Sweeties, 08-16-2005[/#]</quote>

<quote>    In Mexico we have a word for sushi: Bait.
                        [#808080]Jose Simon[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If a person feels he can't communicate, the least he can do is shut up about it.
                        [#808080]Tom Lehrer (1928 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Whenever you take a step forward you are bound to disturb something. You disturb the air as you go forward, you disturb the dust, the ground.
                        [#808080]Indira Gandhi (1917 - 1984)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Good questions outrank easy answers.
                        [#808080]Paul A. Samuelson[/#]</quote>

<quote>    My wife is always trying to get rid of me. The other day she told me to put the garbage out. I said to her I already did. She told me to go and keep an eye on it.
                        [#808080]Rodney Dangerfield (1921 - 2004)[/#]</quote>
</xml>