<xml>
<quote>    Television is the triumph of machine over people.
                        [#808080]Fred Allen (1894 - 1956)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Stay centered by accepting whatever you are doing. This is the ultimate.
                        [#808080]Chuang-tzu (369 BC - 286 BC)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Red meat is NOT bad for you. Now blue-green meat, THAT'S bad for you!
                        [#808080]Tommy Smothers[/#]</quote>

<quote>    But they shall sit every man under his vine and under his fig tree.
                        [#808080]Bible, Micah iv. 4.[/#]</quote>

<quote>    It matters not how strait the gate,
How charged with punishments the scroll,
I am the master of my fate:
I am the captain of my soul.
                        [#808080]William Ernest Henley, From the poem "Invictus"[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Thomas Jefferson still lives.
                        [#808080]John Adams (1735 - 1826), On his bed, not knowing Jefferson had died only a few hours earlier-July 4th, 1826[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Brevity is the soul of wit.
                        [#808080]William Shakespeare (1564 - 1616)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Black holes are where God divided by zero.
                        [#808080]Steven Wright (1955 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Never tell evil of a man, if you do not know it for certainty, and if you know it for a certainty, then ask yourself, 'Why should I tell it?'
                        [#808080]Johann K. Lavater[/#]</quote>

<quote>    An idea is a feat of association.
                        [#808080]Robert Frost (1874 - 1963)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    EXPERIENCE, n. The wisdom that enables us to recognize as an undesirable old acquaintance the folly that we have already embraced.</quote>

<quote>    To one who, journeying through night and fog,
Is mired neck-deep in an unwholesome bog,
Experience, like the rising of the dawn,
Reveals the path that he should not have gone.
Joel Frad Bink
                        [#808080]Ambrose Bierce (1842 - 1914), The Devil's Dictionary[/#]</quote>

<quote>    New Jersey needs a hero. Bon Jovi does not count.
                        [#808080]Kurt Angle, Gold Medal Olympic Wrestler[/#]</quote>

<quote>    When someone says, 'It's not the money, it's the principle of the thing', it's the money.
                        [#808080]Kin Hubbard (1868 - 1930)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Children are likely to live up to what you believe of them.
                        [#808080]Lady Bird Johnson (1912 - 2007)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There is no great genius free from some tincture of madness.
                        [#808080]Seneca (5 BC - 65 AD)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    That's what I consider true generosity. You give your all, and yet you always feel as if it costs you nothing.
                        [#808080]Simone de Beauvoir[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Now cracks a noble heart. Good night sweet prince:
And flights of angels sing thee to thy rest!
                        [#808080]William Shakespeare (1564 - 1616), "Hamlet", Act 5 scene 2[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Unlike those who pretend to be immaculate, fallen angels are usually more intriguing because their earthliness is heavenly.
                        [#808080]Carl Polloi[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Experience is what you get when you don't get what you want.
                        [#808080]Dr. Paul Brown[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The innocence of the intention abates nothing of the mischief of the example.
                        [#808080]Robert Hall[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If we had no faults of our own, we would not take so much pleasure in noticing those of others.
                        [#808080]Francois de La Rochefoucauld (1613 - 1680)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The health of the eye seems to demand a horizon. We are never tired, so long as we can see far enough.
                        [#808080]Ralph Emerson, Nature: Addresses and Lectures[/#]</quote>

<quote>    To get the best out of a man go to what is best in him.
                        [#808080]Daniel Considine[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Education is a kind of continuing dialogue, and a dialogue assumes, in the nature of the case, different points of view.
                        [#808080]Robert Hutchins (1899 - 1977)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I don't know if God exists, but it would be better for His reputation if He didn't.
                        [#808080]Jules Renard (1864 - 1910)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    My Father taught me how to be a man – and not by instilling in me a sense of machismo or an agenda of dominance. He taught me that a real man doesn’t take, he gives; he doesn’t use force, he uses logic; doesn’t play the role of trouble-maker, but rather, trouble-shooter; and most importantly, a real man is defined by what’s in his heart, not his pants.
                        [#808080]Kevin Smith, My Boring Ass Life, 06-01-05[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Millions of men have lived to fight, build palaces and boundaries, shape destinies and societies; but the compelling force of all times has been the force of originality and creation profoundly affecting the roots of human spirit.
                        [#808080]Ansel Adams (1902 - 1984)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    In university they don't tell you that the greater part of the law is learning to tolerate fools.
                        [#808080]Doris Lessing[/#]</quote>
</xml>