<xml>
<quote>    Our Constitution protects aliens, drunks, and U.S. senators.
                        [#808080]Will Rogers (1879 - 1935)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Memory is a giggling sprite and will not be tamed. She takes flight the moment the present becomes the past.
                        [#808080]Real Live Preacher, weblog, 04-29-04[/#]</quote>

<quote>    DANCE, v.i. To leap about to the sound of tittering music, preferably with arms about your neighbor's wife or daughter. There are many kinds of dances, but all those requiring the participation of the two sexes have two characteristics in common: they are conspicuously innocent, and warmly loved by the vicious.
                        [#808080]Ambrose Bierce (1842 - 1914), The Devil's Dictionary[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Determine to live life with flair and laughter.
                        [#808080]Maya Angelou (1928 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Love goes toward love as schoolboys from their books; but love from look, toward school with heavy looks.
                        [#808080]William Shakespeare (1564 - 1616), Romeo and Juliet[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If language is not correct, then what is said is not what is meant; if what is said is not what is meant, then what must be done remains undone; if this remains undone, morals and art will deteriorate; if justice goes astray, the people will stand about in helpless confusion. Hence there must be no arbitrariness in what is said. This matters above everything.
                        [#808080]Confucius (551 BC - 479 BC)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Nobody speaks the truth when there's something they must have.
                        [#808080]Elizabeth Bowen (1899 - 1973)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Rare is the person who can weigh the faults of others without putting his thumb on the scales.
                        [#808080]Byron J. Langenfeld[/#]</quote>

<quote>    ...in song the words tend to lose their significance, do often lose it, while at the other extreme, in current prose it is the musical value that tends to disappear - so that verse stands symmetrically, as it were, between song, on the one hand, and prose on the other - and is thus admirably and delicately balanced between the sensual and the intellectual power of language.
                        [#808080]Paul Valery (1871 - 1945)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    No one who has read official documents needs to be told how easy it is to conceal the essential truth under the apparently candid and all- disclosing phrases of a voluminous and particularizing report....
                        [#808080]Woodrow Wilson (1856 - 1924), _Congressional Government_, p. 109[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Critic, n. A person who boasts himself hard to please because nobody tries to please him.
                        [#808080]Ambrose Bierce (1842 - 1914), The Devil's Dictionary[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There is nothing in the world more powerful than an idea. No weapon can destroy it; no power can conquer it except the power of another idea.
                        [#808080]James Roy Smith[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Men live in a fantasy world. I know this because I am one, and I actually receive my mail there.
                        [#808080]Scott Adams (1957 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    While you're saving your face you're losing your ass.
                        [#808080]Lyndon Baines Johnson[/#]</quote>

<quote>    For Brutus is an honourable man;
    So are they all, all honourable men.
                        [#808080]William Shakespeare (1564 - 1616), "Julius Caesar", Act 3 scene 2[/#]</quote>

<quote>    For a while we pondered whether to take a vacation or get a divorce. We decided that a trip to Bermuda is over in two weeks, but a divorce is something you always have.
                        [#808080]Woody Allen (1935 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    He that is busy is tempted by but one devil; he that is idle, by a legion.
                        [#808080]Thomas Fuller (1608 - 1661), Gnomologia, 1732[/#]</quote>

<quote>    D'you call life a bad job? Never! We've had our ups and downs, we've had our struggles, we've always been poor, but it's been worth it, ay, worth it a hundred times I say when I look round at my children.
                        [#808080]W. Somerset Maugham (1874 - 1965), 'Of Human Bondage', 1915[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Dost thou love life? Then do not squander time, for that's the stuff life is made of.
                        [#808080]Benjamin Franklin (1706 - 1790), 'Poor Richard's Almanack,' June 1746[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Crude, immoral, vulgar and senseless.
                        [#808080]Leo Tolstoy (1828 - 1910)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Every quotation contributes something to the stability or enlargement of the language.
                        [#808080]Samuel Johnson (1709 - 1784)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Only dull people are brilliant at breakfast.
                        [#808080]Oscar Wilde (1854 - 1900), An Ideal Husband, 1893, Act I[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Forgiveness is the healing of wounds caused by another. You choose to let go of a past wrong and no longer be hurt by it. Forgiveness is a strong move to make, like turning your shoulders sideways to walk quickly on a crowded sidewalk. It's your move.
                        [#808080]Real Live Preacher, RealLivePreacher.com Weblog, July 7, 2003[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life. Don't be trapped by dogma - which is living with the results of other people's thinking. Don't let the noise of other's opinions drown out your own inner voice. And most important, have the courage to follow your heart and intuition. They somehow already know what you truly want to become. Everything else is secondary.
                        [#808080]Steve Jobs (1955 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Between two evils, I always pick the one I never tried before.
                        [#808080]Mae West (1892 - 1980), Klondike Annie (1936 film)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    A kiss can be a comma, a question mark, or an exclamation point. That's the basic spelling that every woman ought to know.
                        [#808080]Mistinguette[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Patriots always talk of dying for their country and never of killing for their country.
                        [#808080]Bertrand Russell (1872 - 1970)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Pale Death with impartial tread beats at the poor man's cottage door and at the palaces of kings.
                        [#808080]Horace (65 BC - 8 BC), Odes[/#]</quote>

<quote>    NONSENSE, n. The objections that are urged against this excellent dictionary.
                        [#808080]Ambrose Bierce (1842 - 1914), The Devil's Dictionary[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Music happens to be a form that transcends all languages.
                        [#808080]Herbie Hancock[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The sun, the moon and the stars would have disappeared long ago, had they happened to be within reach of predatory human hands.
                        [#808080]Havelock Ellis (1859 - 1939), "The Dance of Life", 1923[/#]</quote>
</xml>