<xml>
<quote>    There is nothing like dream to create the future. Utopia to-day, flesh and blood tomorrow.
                        [#808080]Victor Hugo (1802 - 1885), Les Miserables, 1862[/#]</quote>

<quote>    A woman's heart is a deep ocean of secrets.
                        [#808080]Gloria Stuart[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I don't think it's the nature of any man to be monogamous. Men are propelled by genetically ordained impulses over which they have no control to distribute thair seed.
                        [#808080]Marlon Brando (1924 - 2004)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If you're not turned on to politics, politics will turn on you.
                        [#808080]Ralph Nader (1934 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    When I'm inspired, I get excited because I can't wait to see what I'll come up with next.
                        [#808080]Dolly Parton[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There are two means of refuge from the miseries of life: music and cats.
                        [#808080]Albert Schweitzer (1875 - 1965)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    May your home always be too small to hold all of your friends.
                        [#808080]Irish Blessing[/#]</quote>

<quote>    To love someone is to identify with them.
                        [#808080]Aristotle (384 BC - 322 BC)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Doubt is the vestibule which all must pass before they can enter the temple of wisdom. When we are in doubt and puzzle out the truth by our own exertions, we have gained something that will stay by us and will serve us again. But if to avoid the trouble of the search we avail ourselves of the superior information of a friend, such knowledge will not remain with us; we have not bought, but borrowed it.
                        [#808080]C. C. Colton[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The easiest kind of relationship for me is with ten thousand people. The hardest is with one.
                        [#808080]Joan Baez (1941 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Tragedy is when I cut my finger. Comedy is when you walk into an open sewer and die.
                        [#808080]Mel Brooks (1926 - )[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Few people think more than two or three times a year. I have made an international reputation for myself by thinking once or twice a week.
                        [#808080]George Bernard Shaw (1856 - 1950)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Tomas did not realize at the time that metaphors are dangerous. Metaphors are not to be trifled with. A single metaphor can give birth to love.
                        [#808080]Milan Kundera (1929 - ), The Unbearable Lightness of Being[/#]</quote>

<quote>    No matter how much you disagree with your kin, if you are a thoroughbred you will not discuss their shortcomings with the neighbors.
                        [#808080]Tom Thompson[/#]</quote>

<quote>    To judge from the notions expounded by theologians, one must conclude that God created most men simply with a view to crowding hell.
                        [#808080]Marquis de Sade[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Act the way you'd like to be and soon you'll be the way you act.
                        [#808080]Dr. George W. Crane[/#]</quote>

<quote>    CUI BONO? What good would that do _me_?
                        [#808080]Ambrose Bierce (1842 - 1914), The Devil's Dictionary[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Never argue with an idiot, because they will only bring you down to their level and beat you by experience.
                        [#808080]John Guerrero[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Women are not inherently passive or peaceful. We're not inherently anything but human.
                        [#808080]Robin Morgan[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Make your life a mission - not an intermission.
                        [#808080]Arnold Glasgow[/#]</quote>

<quote>    How is the Empire?
                        [#808080]George V, last words, 21 January 1936.[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If you don't get a kick out of the job you are doing you'd better hunt another one.
                        [#808080]Samuel Vauclain[/#]</quote>

<quote>    For death begins with life's first breath, and life begins at touch of death.
                        [#808080]John Oxenham[/#]</quote>

<quote>    We're a sentimental people. We like a few kind words better than millions of dollars given in a humiliating way.
                        [#808080]Gamal Abdel Nasser (1918 - 1970), on refusing Western economic assistance, 'Realites,' January 20, 1969[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Innocence dwells with Wisdom, but never with Ignorance.
                        [#808080]William Blake (1757 - 1827)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I am where I am because I believe in all possibilities.
                        [#808080]Whoopi Goldberg[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Regret for the things we did can be tempered by time; it is regret for the things we did not do that is inconsolable.
                        [#808080]Sidney J. Harris[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The only mystery about the cat is why it ever decided to become a domesticated animal
                        [#808080]Sir Compton MacKenzie[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There are two great rules of life, the one general and the other particular. The first is that everyone can in the end, get what he wants, if he only tries. That is the general rule. The particular rule is that every individual is, more or less, an exception to the rule.
                        [#808080]Samuel Butler (1835 - 1902)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    PRISON, n. A place of punishments and rewards. The poet assures us that --\n
\n
    "Stone walls do not a prison make,"
\n
    but a combination of the stone wall, the political parasite and the moral instructor is no garden of sweets.
                        [#808080]Ambrose Bierce (1842 - 1914), The Devil's Dictionary[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I was brought up by very witty people who were dealing with quite difficult things - disease and death... I was brought up by people who tended to giggle at funerals.
                        [#808080]Emma Thompson, Vanity Fair[/#]</quote>
</xml>