<xml>
<quote>    When in doubt, have two guys come through the door with guns.
                        [#808080]Raymond Chandler (1888 - 1959)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Loss of empathy might well be the most enduring and deep-cutting scar of all, the silent blade of an unseen enemy, tearing at our hearts and stealing more than our strength.
                        [#808080]R. A. Salvatore, Drizzt Do'Urden in "The Silent Blade"[/#]</quote>

<quote>    There is no worse heresy than that the office sanctifies the holder of it.
                        [#808080]Lord Acton, Letter to Bishop Mandell Creighton, 5 Apr 1887[/#]</quote>

<quote>    It takes two to speak the truth--one to speak and the other to hear.
                        [#808080]Henry David Thoreau (1817 - 1862)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Happiness comes of the capacity to feel deeply, to enjoy simply, to think freely, to risk life, to be needed.
                        [#808080]Storm Jameson[/#]</quote>

<quote>    What good is money if it can't inspire terror in your fellow man?
                        [#808080]Matt Groening (1954 - ), The Simpsons[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Most of our imports come from other countries.
                        [#808080]George W. Bush (1946 - ), Robin Williams, Live on Broadway[/#]</quote>

<quote>    We are the living links in a life force that moves and plays around and through us, binding the deepest soils with the farthest stars.
                        [#808080]Alan Chadwick[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The only way to succeed is to make people hate you.
                        [#808080]Josef von Sternberg[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Only if we understand, will we care. Only if we care, will we help. Only if we help shall all be saved.
                        [#808080]Jane Goodall[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Proportion your expenses to what you have, not what you expect.
                        [#808080]English Proverb[/#]</quote>

<quote>    The art of life lies in a constant readjustment to our surroundings.
                        [#808080]Okakura Kakuzo[/#]</quote>

<quote>    If you want to see what children can do, you must stop giving them things.
                        [#808080]Norman Douglas[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Unprovided with original learning, unformed in the habits of thinking, unskilled in the arts of composition, I resolved to write a book.
                        [#808080]Edward Gibbon (1737 - 1794)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    I'm better than dirt. Well, most kinds of dirt, not that fancy store-bought dirt... I can't compete with that stuff.
                        [#808080]Matt Groening (1954 - ), The Simpsons[/#]</quote>

<quote>    My punishment is greater than I can bear
                        [#808080]Bible, Genesis iv. 13.[/#]</quote>

<quote>    What I said never changed anyone. What they understood did.
                        [#808080]Unknown[/#]</quote>

<quote>    A facility for quotation covers the absence of original thought.
                        [#808080]Dorothy L. Sayers (1893 - 1957), Lord Peter Wimsey in "Gaudy Night"[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Example is not the main thing in influencing others. It is the only thing.
                        [#808080]Albert Schweitzer (1875 - 1965)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Well, all I know is what I read in the papers.
                        [#808080]Will Rogers (1879 - 1935)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Somewhere, something incredible is waiting to be known.
                        [#808080]Carl Sagan (1934 - 1996)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Adults are just obsolete children and the hell with them.
                        [#808080]Dr. Seuss (1904 - 1991)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Creative powers can just as easily turn out to be destructive. It rests solely with the moral personality whether they apply themselves to good things or to bad. And if this is lacking, no teacher can supply it or take its place
                        [#808080]Carl Jung (1875 - 1961)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Maturity is the ability to do a job whether or not you are supervised, to carry money without spending it and to bear an injustice without wanting to get even.
                        [#808080]Ann Landers (1918 - 2002)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Unless you are prepared yourself to profit by your chance, the opportunity will only make you ridiculous. A great occasion is valuable to you in proportion as you have educated yourself to make use of it.
                        [#808080]Orison Swett Marden (1850 - 1924)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Let us so live that when we come to die even the undertaker will be sorry.
                        [#808080]Mark Twain (1835 - 1910)[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Neither a borrower nor a lender be; For loan oft loses both itself and friend; And borrowing dulls the edge of husbandry.
                        [#808080]William Shakespeare (1564 - 1616), 'Hamlet,' Act I, Scene iii[/#]</quote>

<quote>    You look after your empire; I'll look after myself.
                        [#808080]Princess Margaret of Great Britain, "Biography" TV series. Host: Mike Wallace[/#]</quote>

<quote>    It's a recession when your neighbor loses his job; it's a depression when you lose yours.
                        [#808080]Harry S Truman (1884 - 1972), in Observer, April 13, 1958[/#]</quote>

<quote>    Only eyes washed by tears can see clearly.
                        [#808080]Louis M. Mann[/#]</quote>
</xml>